List<Map<String, dynamic>> InfControlPartOneQuestions = [
  {
    'question':
        'Which microorganism is responsible for most hospital-acquired infections (HAIs)?',
    'answers': [
      'Escherichia coli.',
      'Staphylococcus aureus.',
      'Clostridium difficile.',
      'Pseudomonas aeruginosa.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 1,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'What is the primary mode of transmission for tuberculosis (TB)?',
    'answers': [
      'Droplet transmission.',
      'Airborne transmission.',
      'Contact transmission.',
      'Vector-borne transmission.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 1,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'Which of the following personal protective equipment (PPE) is not typically required for contact precautions?',
    'answers': ['Gown.', 'Mask.', 'Gloves.', 'Face shield.',],
    'correctIndex': 1,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'Which of the following is the most effective method for hand hygiene?',
    'answers': [
      'Hand sanitizer with at least 60% alcohol.',
      'Soap and water for at least 20 seconds.',
      'Antimicrobial wipes.',
      'Rubbing hands with a dry cloth.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 1,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'What is the recommended minimum air changes per hour (ACH) for a negative pressure isolation room?',
    'answers': ['6 ACH.', '10 ACH.', '12 ACH.', '15 ACH.',],
    'correctIndex': 3,
  },
  {
    'question': 'Which of the following diseases requires droplet precautions?',
    'answers': ['MRSA.', 'Influenza.', 'Tuberculosis.', 'Norovirus.',],
    'correctIndex': 1,
  },
  {
    'question': 'What is the incubation period for hepatitis A?',
    'answers': ['1-2 days.', '1-2 weeks.', '2-4 weeks.', '6-8 weeks.',],
    'correctIndex': 2,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'Which of the following is an example of a healthcare-associated infection (HAI)?',
    'answers': [
      'Chickenpox.',
      'Malaria.',
      'Urinary tract infection from a catheter.',
      'Common cold.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 2,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'What is the primary purpose of an autoclave in infection control?',
    'answers': [
      'Hand hygiene.',
      'Disinfection of surfaces.',
      'Sterilization of equipment.',
      'Wastewater treatment.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 2,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'Which of the following is an example of a vector-borne disease?',
    'answers': ['HIV.', 'West Nile virus.', 'Hepatitis C.', 'Influenza.',],
    'correctIndex': 1,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'Which of the following is not considered a standard precaution in infection control?',
    'answers': [
      'Hand hygiene.',
      'Respiratory hygiene.',
      'Needlestick precautions.',
      'Use of PPE.'
    ],
    'correctIndex': 2,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'What is the recommended temperature for storing perishable medications in a healthcare facility\'s refrigerator?',
    'answers': [
      '2-8°C (36-46°F).',
      '10-15°C (50-59°F).',
      '-10°C (14°F).',
      '25-30°C (77-86°F).',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 0,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'Which of the following is the most effective method to prevent the spread of C. difficile in healthcare settings?',
    'answers': [
      'Isolation precautions.',
      'Routine antibiotic use.',
      'Frequent handwashing with soap and water.',
      'Environmental cleaning with water only.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 2,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'Which of the following bloodborne pathogens is primarily transmitted through sexual contact and intravenous drug use?',
    'answers': ['Hepatitis B.', 'Hepatitis C.', 'HIV.', 'Tuberculosis.',],
    'correctIndex': 2,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'What is the appropriate action for a nurse who accidentally experiences a needlestick injury while caring for a patient with known HIV infection?',
    'answers': [
      'Notify the supervisor but continue working.',
      'Immediately start antiretroviral therapy.',
      'Wash the wound and observe for symptoms.',
      'Ignore the injury if the needle is clean.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 2,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'Which of the following immunizations is recommended for healthcare workers to prevent influenza transmission?',
    'answers': [
      'MMR vaccine.',
      'Hepatitis B vaccine.',
      'Varicella vaccine.',
      'Influenza vaccine.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 3,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'What is the correct order for removing personal protective equipment (PPE) after caring for a patient with isolation precautions?',
    'answers': [
      'Gloves, gown, mask, goggles.',
      'Goggles, gloves, gown, mask.',
      'Mask, gown, gloves, goggles.',
      'Gown, gloves, goggles, mask.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 0,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'Which of the following is not a recommended practice for preventing surgical site infections (SSIs)?',
    'answers': [
      'Prophylactic antibiotic administration.',
      'Preoperative shaving of the surgical site.',
      'Strict aseptic technique during surgery.',
      'Surgical hand scrub before the procedure.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 1,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'What is the recommended duration for contact precautions when caring for a patient with methicillin-resistant Staphylococcus aureus (MRSA)?',
    'answers': [
      '24 hours.',
      'Until the patient tests negative.',
      'Until the patient is discharged.',
      '48 hours after symptom resolution.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 3,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'What is the primary purpose of a surgical mask in preventing the spread of infections?',
    'answers': [
      'Protecting the wearer from airborne pathogens.',
      'Protecting the patient from the wearer\'s respiratory secretions.',
      'Filtering out bacteria and viruses.',
      'Maintaining sterile conditions in the operating room.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 1,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'Which of the following is the most common source of Clostridium difficile spores in healthcare settings?',
    'answers': [
      'Airborne transmission.',
      'Contaminated surfaces and equipment.',
      'Ingestion of contaminated food.',
      'Sexual contact.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 1,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'What is the correct sequence for donning personal protective equipment (PPE)?',
    'answers': [
      'Gown, mask, gloves, goggles.',
      'Goggles, mask, gown, gloves.',
      'Gloves, gown, mask, goggles.',
      'Mask, goggles, gown, gloves.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 2,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'Which of the following is a recommended practice to prevent ventilator-associated pneumonia (VAP)?',
    'answers': [
      'Frequent use of sedatives to keep patients calm.',
      'Routine endotracheal tube changes.',
      'Elevating the head of the bed to 30-45 degrees.',
      'Administering broad-spectrum antibiotics prophylactically.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 2,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'What is the primary goal of the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC) in the context of infection control?',
    'answers': [
      'Researching new infectious diseases.',
      'Monitoring vaccine development.',
      'Preventing and controlling the spread of infections.',
      'Promoting hand hygiene in the community.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 2,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'Which of the following is not a component of the chain of infection?',
    'answers': [
      'Portal of entry.',
      'Reservoir.',
      'Fomite.',
      'Mode of transmission.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 3,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'What is the primary purpose of a spore test in autoclave quality control?',
    'answers': [
      'Monitoring autoclave temperature.',
      'Testing autoclave pressure.',
      'Verifying sterilization effectiveness.',
      'Measuring autoclave volume.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 2,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'What type of isolation precautions are necessary for a patient with suspected or confirmed tuberculosis (TB)?',
    'answers': [
      'Contact precautions.',
      'Droplet precautions.',
      'Airborne precautions.',
      'Standard precautions.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 2,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'Which of the following vaccines is not routinely administered to healthcare workers?',
    'answers': [
      'Hepatitis B.',
      'Measles, mumps, and rubella (MMR).',
      'Varicella.',
      'Polio.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 3,
  },
  {
    'question': 'What is the primary mode of transmission for the Ebola virus?',
    'answers': ['Airborne.', 'Droplet.', 'Contact.', 'Vector-borne.',],
    'correctIndex': 3,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'Which of the following is an example of a device-associated healthcare-associated infection (DA-HAI)?',
    'answers': [
      'Ventilator-associated pneumonia (VAP).',
      'Surgical site infection (SSI).',
      'Catheter-associated urinary tract infection (CAUTI).',
      'Central line-associated bloodstream infection (CLABSI).',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 3,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'What is the recommended technique for removing a contaminated gown after caring for a patient on contact precautions?',
    'answers': [
      'Pull the gown over the head.',
      'Untie the neck and waist ties simultaneously.',
      'Remove gloves first, then untie the gown.',
      'Leave the gown on until the end of the shift.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 1,
  },
];
